Wow, it's like the thumbnail came to life.
That behind me is a visual hook.
It's something that I'm using not only in
organic content, but we've used it in the
thumbnail for this video. Now,
just thought I'd remind you earlier in the
video
that the majority of you
are lazy fucking pricks.
What I mean by is we're running a campaign
this week for Amazon Prime, so I decided
to get a sign made. Not only that,
I also wrapped the windscreen of my
car. And any of you
that have seen "Talladega Nights" will
appreciate that.
So you might be wondering why I went to
the effort of having balloons made, a sign
produced,
and getting the car wrapped to send people
to a website
where we make less money per can of
Nutonic than we would from our own.
Well, in this video,
I'll explain it to you so you can
understand the basic
economics of, well, online marketing.
First things first, effort.
I spent an afternoon out of my day getting
that made.
Same with some of my best performing
YouTube videos where I've got the big
stack of
Coke Zeros, had to go to the shop
and had to buy them.
Or other incredible performing videos like
the creatine gummy video, where I had to
send off 10 different competitors to
Eurofins to get tested
and wait months for the
report to come back.
The more effort you put in, people see.
The thumbnail for this, people
are going to go,
"Did he really make a sign or is
that AI?" And my belief is,
in a world where everything is made of AI,
going back
to analog is how you stand out.
Had a big issue this week where quite
clearly some
emails were being written by Claude in a
business that I own and
[laughs] I was fucked off because humans
are smart and they know when it's AI.
So back to this point.
When you're running a business,
two things you need to
consider. First of all,
you're either selling a product
or a service.
Now, the majority of you I know
are coaches or physios or accountants.
You're selling a service, and this
is a product,
and you might not have a product
for a few years,
but it's still worth understanding this
because, well, it's
fucking interesting. Now,
the one thing I would say
is never discount a service,
but you can discount a product because
if Declan here was doing video editing and
he discounted his rates by 10%...
How did I put an N back to front?
I'm 37. Anyway, we'll leave it.
Makes me look humble.
Let's imagine this
is the amount I pay for Declan for video
editing.
Don't worry, he earns way more, and I
was ill last week. Enjoy.
It's like holiday pay, that.
Unfortunately for Declan, all
that money isn't his to
take home. He has his costs of living,
probably his food bill is
massive if you've ever seen the amount of
breakfast fucking buffet.
He's got his taxes,
he's got his equipment, he's got-
Girlfriend.
[laughs] Girlfriend.
So let's say this bit here
is his take home.
But if Declan here ends up shaving 10% off
his hourly rate, he actually
takes about 20% off the amount of money he
gets to take home.
So although it seems like a 10% discount,
it's 20% less.
He now needs to work 20% more to earn the
same money.
And what that means for Declan is
that poor guy there
is going to have to cancel
plans with his girlfriend,
work all day Saturday to earn the same
money that he did
before. However,
when it comes to a product, every cost,
every margin, it's
actually not a big deal to reduce your
margin as long as one thing happens, and
what's that, Declan? You improve volume.
So if I was to draw that for you,
let's imagine...
And by the way, a lot of you, you're like,
if you don't run your own business, or
let's say you support the Greens party,
you might think profit is bad or the fact
we're making money off it.
Why can't they do it for free?
Why can't they do a not-for-profit
organization? Why can't they be a charity?
Well, you need margins,
you need a surplus of cash so you can pay
employees.
If they perform well,
you need money to give employees bonuses,
you need to pay
their pensions,
you need to look after them.
So you have the employee side of things,
but also to expand.
Those of you complaining
that we don't have cans in your territory
yet, we need
money to produce that,
to make new flavors,
to go into new product development.
So considering that Chris
and I don't take a salary from the
business, just be
happy. Now, that square radius there,
if we reduce our
margins... And by the way,
if you're watching this,
there's going to be a link for
Prime Day where you can go
and get mad discounts on Nutonic.
But also, if you're in the UK,
head to TikTok, I think it's cheaper.
Do your due diligence. It depends.
You can't call them the CCP, Declan.
I've told you that.
They're called TikTok
and Bezos' billionaire buddies.
Whichever one you prefer, fine.
If our margins come down,
as long as our volume
increases,
we get the same surface area of money.
So Amazon Prime Day to us
is just about moving those variables
around.
As long as volume goes up, we're good.
Now, the way that we can improve volume
is by sending traffic to Amazon Prime,
which is twofold. So for me to do that,
one, I need something novel in content.
I've been making content 10 years.
People are sick to death of seeing the
same fucking setup.
"Oh,
it's James Smith just ranting about his
fucking product again.
Tell us more about calorie deficits." It's
been 10 years. Relax.
So I made the sign
and the balloons because I know this
is going to
increase the amount of impressions
that I can get on social media sending
people to
it. For me, Abraham Lincoln once said,
"If you've got seven hours to chop down a
tree,
spend the first three hours sharpening the
ax." And that's what we're doing
here. Yesterday, no cameras on, I decided,
right, we're going to make assets, have
fun.
We're going to improve the amount of
impressions because more impressions, the
more people we're going to get,
and we'll go through this quickly.
First things first,
we send a certain amount of people to
Prime Day, a certain
amount of people are going to purchase.
Cool.
Not everyone that goes to Prime Day
is going to purchase.
Now, out of some people that
are purchasing,
I think they get 20% discount.
We can improve people that
are getting a sub because I think we're
offering a
30% discount. Now, can you subscribe
and cancel after the first month
and still get
the discount? Yeah.
Why am I telling you that?
Because I haven't lied to you yet.
Why start now? And also, subscribe
and cancel.
That's fine because you're going to
cancel,
you're going to crack a can of Nutonic.
You're going to go,
"That's fantastic." Some of you
are going to go back and you're
going to bring the subscription back,
but then some of you aren't
and you're going
to go back and have had a Ghost
and you're going to drink it
and you're going to
go, "Wow, that is inferior.
I have descended and I am going to go back
to the
Nutonic subscription to ascend into a giga
chad." Talking in your language.
Then at the bottom of it, we
are going to acquire some CFLs, which
is customer for
life. So out of some people
that go to Prime Day,
they're going to go going, "I'm
just going for a discount because it's
cheaper than fucking Ghost or Nocco or
whatever other piss you drink."
And then out of them, some of you
are going to
purchase and some of you only went to
purchase, but some of you end up doing a
subscription and then some of you become
customer for life and you bleed bloody
Nutonic. You're the type of people saying,
"Give me a T-shirt, I'll wear it." And
by the way, I am doing that.
As you may not known, I've
adapted into Invest,
I've invested into Adapt, and I've ordered
500 of these vests
but with Nutonic on the front.
Do you know how much they're going to
cost? Nothing.
I'm giving them away for free.
I probably will give them to Adapt
customers first, so
if you don't do jujitsu,
soz. So we've got the funnel on one side.
These are going to be people that
are familiar to the ecosystem,
the business,
Chris, myself, whatever.
But there's also going to be an Amazon
chart and this
is why we're sucking off Amazon a bit.
This is why we're going skiing, Declan.
Do you know what skiing is?
Wanking off two blokes at the same time.
What, you've never done that?
Oh, you didn't play rugby, did you?
You didn't play rugby, did you?
So the more we can do this,
the more we are going to increase velocity
to
Amazon Prime.
Now there's going to be a leaderboard on
Amazon Prime of which
businesses are doing the best.
And basically,
out of all those businesses,
whichever one can suck off their audience
the most and send the most velocity to
do this because all of this suits Amazon
because they make a markup per
purchase.
So if we can get this going red hot
and we're sending traffic like pew
We're going to climb up the ranks,
and who knows? We'll be sat there.
Someone who doesn't really know the brand
that well is going to come across, and
they're going to go, "That looks cool.
I'm buying some." Let me give you an
example of that, Declan.
Dylan Page, you know him?
Let's show everyone.
If you're not following Dylan Page,
I don't know where you're getting your
news
from. 19.6 million followers, this guy.
Okay, guys.
Major breaking news. It is- Prime Day.
See how I did that?
Now, I'm going to go to my Instagram DMs.
Your wife's in me DMs.
Boy, you tell about a few Nutonix,
can't you? Your wife's in me DMs.
You excited for the McGregor fight?
I sent him a bit of love, 2024.
Said, "Your TikTok is an absolute weapon,
bro." Do you know why?
Because I'm the type of guy that
if I see something I like,
I'm telling you.
You got a good set of legs, bro,
I like your quads.
If you got a hot missus, well done.
If I'm going to talk to your missus,
I'm going
to say, "Well done, your parents." Okay?
If you've ever got the opportunity to
compliment someone,
I still go up to people
in nice cars, not as nice as mine,
I still say,
"Nice car." I see a young lad in an
M2, I'm like, "Love your car, bro.
Love your car." Make them feel good,
right?
That's why.
If we take one thing from this video,
it's not that you need to go buy
Nutonic, it's dish out positivity
when you can.
Give, receive, pay it forward. Anyway,
let me read this out.
Let me read this out, okay? "Bro,
I meant to message you yesterday because I
thought you'd like to hear this.
So I've been smashing this new drink I
found on
Amazon, and I even told Prime,
'Don't worry about sending me any more.' I
then was told that you and Chris made it.
Man, fricking so well to you guys.
You've created an amazing product." He
didn't
know that Chris and I had made Nutonic.
He saw it on Amazon, went to click on it,
liked the branding, liked the
message. Maybe it was the ingredients,
maybe it was the branding, maybe it
was the
eye. Who knows?
Maybe he'd subconsciously seen it
somewhere and he ended up
purchasing it. Then what happens there,
Declan,
is when they click because they see
it in the charts, oh my God.
We're helping Amazon, Amazon's helping us.
The velocity is paying back.
We're playing the game. Now,
I can't be bought.
Amazon tried offering me a paid post for
Amazon Prime Day, and they came up a
little bit light,
£82,000 short of what I would've done it
for, because I don't do
paid ads, but for a certain figure,
I would.
A certain figure, I'd go,
"I don't do paid ads," but I do now.
GT3 RS ain't going to pay for itself,
is it? That's why we're playing the game.
Prime don't own me,
but I understand the ecosystem. This
is what it's about.
That's why we've gone to the effort.
That's why we've done the campaigns.
That's why we've done the balloons,
because effort equals outcome.
I'm not even sure that makes sense.
It's pretty interesting, isn't it?
What do you think about ecosystems?
Do you know that?
Would you be going on Prime Day looking
for a good deal?
If you didn't know much about Prime Day,
that's how you can tell someone's getting
paid too much. That sign
and all the tactics about this campaign
that I've used for
Prime Day is all part of mastering
short-form content, which
is why I've created
Short-Form Content Mastery.
There's going to be a link to it in the
description.
Or if you don't want to give me your
money, if you found this interesting,
I want
to give you 30 more pieces of nuggets
that I'll deliver to you one a day via
email.
All you need to do
is click the link in the description,
30 days, 30 ways.
Give me 30 days to improve your business.
I'll give you a, "Fuck me,
never thought of that," every single day.
If not, watch this video here,
because YouTube recommends you'll really
like it.